thesimpletruth.in 2018-12-14

# Privacy Policy | The Simple Truth

Our privacy policy will let you know what are the information that are collected when you visit our company’s site or send us an email and how the information are being used by us

Our web server will record certain information when you visit our site.

 We track your

IP address

Username (if you are a registered user)

URLs (that you have access).

The status of your request

URLs of the WebPages that guided you to our site.

Count of the bytes transferred and received.

**USER  REGISTRATION**

We have introduced user registration option on our site that allows the visitors those who wanted to post contents in our site. To register in our webpage you ought to submit your first name, last name, your email id and photo if needed. We will publish your first post along with your post.

Google  Analytics

We analyze the usage of our website through Google Analytics Software by  collecting information anonymously from the visitor.

The information that are collected includes IP address, a location of the network and also the geographic location.

We access all  information  from the user and  we do not collect personal information from the user such as name, contact information, financial

information etc.

cookies

cookies that are stored on your hard drive will be later user to track information about the usage, as mention above,  Google Analytics will allow cookies on the hard disk. 

email

we record your emails if you send us or submit to us while during the registration process. We always use email during this process in which you have provided us.

Disclosure of information to third parties.

We don’t lend, sell or disclose any information that we obtained to the third party. We might disclose your information to our employees, agents, consultants if needed.

Websites

We may have links to other websites or recourses that I include websites of organizations and much more. We are not reasonable for the private policy of our sponsors, advertisers, vendors for which we offer hyperlinks and access as well.

 Data security

We have procedures to protect information that we collect online.  Though we have protection methods we do not guarantee the security we collected as of the database as the security system is impenetrable.

Notification and privacy policy

We review security measures and privacy policy of our company only on periodic basic and we modify the policy of our company if needed and we may change or update the privacy policy of the company.  We will notify you when the changes are made in the policy.
